IS THAT PSYCHIC? [screaming]
>> YES. OVER HERE. ON THE SIDE. ON THE
SIDE.
Right here.
YEAH.
GODDAMN.
>> IT'S BEEN [laughter] OVER A DECADE SINCE
I TOUCHED THIS STAGE.
>> YEAH, COCO.
>> [screaming]
>> OH MY GOD.
>> COCO, I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> IT FEELS GOOD TO BE HERE. FIRST OF ALL,
LET ME JUST I NEED Y'ALL TO GET INTO
SOME [\h__\h] RIGHT QUICK. WHEN I LEFT HERE,
I WAS 275 LB. Y'ALL BETTER CHECK THIS
[\h__\h] OUT right here, GOD DAMN.
YES.
THIS IS CALLED LETTING GO AND LETTING
GOD, HONEY.
THIS IS CALLED NOT LETTING NOBODY SORRY
ass son stress ME THE [\h__\h] OUT.
THIS IS CALLED MONJARO, [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> BABY, I'M TELLING YOU IT'S IT'S SO FUNNY
BECAUSE I YOU KNOW I DIDN'T REALIZE I
HAD LOST so much weight UNTIL I CAME OUT
HERE AND EVERYBODY WAS LIKE, "DAMN,
COCO, YOU LOOK GOOD. YOU LOST SO MUCH
WEIGHT." AND THEN I THOUGHT I'D LOOK AT
THE PICTURES OF MY OLD SELF AND I
REALIZED I AIN'T have no [\h__\h]
friends.
Cuz these [\h__\h] HAD ME WALKING AROUND
HOLLYWOOD looking like Precious Jr.
AND I YEAH, I SAID IT. SOME OF Y'ALL
NEED TO CHECK YOUR FRIENDSHIPS.
GOT YOU OUT HERE SMILING in pictures for
seven chins and [\h__\h]
Sweating bacon grease.
Letting [\h__\h] move IN YOU WOULD NEVER
TALK TO IN REAL LIFE.
>> [laughter]
>> I WENT TO ATLANTA AND GOT MY GODDAMN
SELF-WORTH.
I WENT DOWN there and realized that hey,
I had something in common that you know
that THAT'S NOT VERY COMMON IN ATLANTA.
I was born WITHOUT A PENIS.
>> [cheering]
>> OH, I'M SORRY, HONEY. I DON'T KNOW HOW
HOW how LA don't you know how LA don't
tripped out there, but you know coming
from Atlanta, honey, I I be trying to
tell these brothers y'all better stop
asking for a bad [\h__\h] If you do, you
better ask that [\h__\h] for a third grade
school picture.
Cuz honey, I live in ATL, ain't nothing
what it seems.
>> [laughter]
>> These [\h__\h] be walking around thinking
they got bad ass Bethany. THAT
[\h__\h] NAME BRAD.
HONEY, YOU THINK SHE GOT a fat monkey?
Them nuts. SHE DONE LEARNED how to tuck
them [\h__\h] perfectly.
Got me at home looking IN THE MIRROR
GOING, "DAMN, MAYBE I SHOULD GO GET A
DICK. I I DON'T KNOW. I
>> [laughter]
>> YEAH, I'M CALLING IT WHAT I SEE IT.
YOU BE HAPPY WITH A woman with some
stretch marks, a little food pile, some
hormonal changes, going through
menopause.
Up here wanting these perfect [\h__\h]
and [\h__\h] Uh-uh, you don't want to do
it.
Y'all be so fascinated be looking at the
woman's titties and ass thinking, "Damn,
she badder than a motherfucker." Let me
tell you something, men. Learn how to
shut the [\h__\h] up cuz see y'all be out
here talking. See, that's the problem.
We're in a sassy [\h__\h] apocalypse right
now.
>> [laughter]
>> And it's men that as my daddy say got
[\h__\h] TEETH. Y'ALL TALK TOO MUCH.
Y'all are sitting on the internet
talking ABOUT WHAT A WOMAN GOT TO BE,
how she got to look, how she got to walk
to be a damn HIGH VALUE WOMAN. WE AIN'T
THE ONES LISTENING TO YOU. WE DON'T GIVE
A DAMN.
IT'S IT'S THEM OTHER ONES RUNNING DOWN
TO DR. MIAMI, DR. Curves getting all
that [\h__\h] you want. Then your ass don't
know the difference. You walking out the
Blue Flame out the strip club at 1:00 in
the MORNING WITH A BAD ASS STALLION ON
YOUR ARM. Chest all swole. YOUR BOYS
LIKE, "DUDE!" I'LL BE WALKING BY SMOOTH
AS HELL TRYING to help you out. "What's
up, nigger?"
>> [cheering]
>> You so fixated on titties and ass this
man DONE BOUGHT. YOU DON'T REALIZE THIS
[\h__\h] GOT A SIZE 15 SHOE.
YOU DON'T KNOW THIS HAVE A JAWLINE.
AIN'T NO WOMAN'S FACE THAT STRONG.
HALF OF IT JOLLY RANCHERS LIKE RAISINS.
>> [cheering]
>> HANDS BIG AS A [\h__\h]
>> EVERY FINGERNAIL TIP IS A THUMBNAIL. WHY
YOUR PINKY SO BIG?
OH, [\h__\h] You need to go find you a nice
regular WOMAN. THAT'S YOUR BEST BET
right now.
And what make me even MADDER IS THAT I
KEEP it 100. I'm 53 years old. I'm a
grown ass woman.
And I want a grown ass man, but it seem
like all the men my AGE ALL OF A SUDDEN
WANT TO TRY TO GO BACKWARDS.
Trying to date somebody daughter.
And my thing is this, that's cute and
all, you know, but sir, you you 55 years
old. That ship done sailed, Mr. Otis.
You don't need a bad [\h__\h] right now cuz
that bad [\h__\h] can't save your life.
Starkisha don't know what to do when she
see you signs of a stroke.
I don't think any man over 50 should be
dating no [\h__\h] with Isha in her name.
ISHA CAN'T SAVE YOUR LIFE.
You need to FIND YOU A HEIFER WITH A
NAME THAT match yours, like Edith,
Ethel, Mildred,
WANDA, A [\h__\h] WITH TWO NAMES, LULA MAE,
ANNA MAE, SUSAN MAE.
A [\h__\h] that know how to keep
peppermints in her purse.
Know how to GIVE YOU CRUSHED ICE CUZ
YOUR IRON LOW. YOU GOT PEPPERMINTS? I
KNEW YOU DID. I see you, Gloria. I see
you, Gloria.
I can ALWAYS SPOT A GLORIA IN AN
AUDIENCE.
The hell you going to DO WITH A
STARKISHA? SHE CAN'T SAVE YOUR LIFE.
Now your ass sitting UP IN MR. CHILD'S,
YOU HAVING A WHOLE STROKE, THIS YOUNG
[\h__\h] START DOING A TIK TOK.
OH MY GOD, WHY YOUR FACE DOING like
that?
Oh my god,
what's wrong with your
hand? Why your hand like this though?
WHAT'S WRONG?
HOLD ON, WE ABOUT TO GO VIRAL. PERIOD.
PERIOD.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU DYING LIKE A MOFO, THIS LITTLE
HEIFER DONE made you a boomerang.
>> [laughter]
>> Dude.
You need to find you a [\h__\h] that know
how TO PUT SOME SWEET LORD IN YOUR
TONGUE, GET YOUR A1C UP.
>> [cheering]
>> Hell is wrong WITH YOU OUT HERE.
Trying to compete with these YOUNG
DUDES, LOOKING LIKE A DAMN FOOL.
YOU AIN'T FOOLING NOBODY, WILLIAM.
Out here putting all that beige in your
hair, looking like Count Dracula.
Then you got the early white chalk
outline, looking like a whole autopsy on
your forehead.
TALK ABOUT YOU STILL GOT IT, TRYING TO
PUT ON SOME JORDANS.
SOME PUMAS. KNOW IT DAMN WELL YOUR FEET
[\h__\h] UP.
>> [screaming]
>> YOU CAN'T WEAR SOFT SOLE SHOES. IF YOU
DO, THEY BETTER BE ROCKPORTS.
HUSHPUPPIES, SKETCHERS.
And you better not have NO LACES. KNOW
YOUR ARTHRITIS [\h__\h] UP, IT NEED TO BE
ALL VELCRO. Zzz zzz zzz zzz I said,
"Hear you when you're coming."
And I'm going TO TALK TO SOME OF MY
GLORIAS IN the house. I don't mean you,
girl, you good.
I'm talking about these other heifers in
here that's my age trying to escape
being a auntie. SEE, WHAT YOU FAIL TO
REALIZE, HONEY, auntie is a bad javana.
That means that you've been through some
[\h__\h] seen some [\h__\h] learned some [\h__\h]
experienced some [\h__\h] and you do not
LOOK LIKE THE [\h__\h] YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH.
>> [cheering]
>> THAT'S WHAT A AUNTIE MEANS. I AM A PROUD
DAMN AUNTIE.
>> [applause]
>> I GET SO MAD WHEN I SEE women my age out
here trying to compete with Scar Keisha.
You out here 55 years old with a catsuit
on and a KITTEN HEEL.
[\h__\h] THAT DON'T GO TOGETHER.
IS THAT FASHION NOVA AND A NATURALIZER?
Is that Shein and a Aerosole?
I can see your panty line, Lorraine. I
know you pee when you giggle.
You 60 years old with them long ASS
EYELASHES ON. KNOW YOUR ASS GOT
GLAUCOMA.
EVERY TIME YOU BLINK, THE WHOLE DAY
CHANGE. DAY, NIGHT, DAY, NIGHT. YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS.
EVERYTHING YOU LOOK AT LOOK LIKE JAIL.
[\h__\h] YOU LOCKED UP.
I'M TIRED.
I'M TIRED. I'M GOING TO
GET some [\h__\h] off
Get off my damn nerves trying to blend
in with the young people at a day party.
We see you Shirley.
The young girls walking in with a hand
fan cuz it's cute. You got a house FAN
FOR HOT FLASHES.
[\h__\h] THAT AIN'T THE SAME.
NOW YOU POSTED UP AT A DJ BOOTH. THAT'S
THE ONLY PLACE you can find a a plug.
You trying to holler at white ears
through the fan. Hi, my name Shirley.
You want to come over? I got some greens
on the stove, baby.
You know go find your ass a Soul Train
cruise or gospel brunch.
Out here busting the [\h__\h] out of us.
>> [laughter]
>> AND I WILL SAY THIS, IT'S HARD BEING AN
AUNTIE NOW CUZ I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING
ON, HONEY, but I know I ain't the only
woman in here of a certain age. It feels
like every time she go outside, the only
thing they try to holler at her is a
[\h__\h] she could have gave birth
to.
I don't know what's going on. These
little white ears want to misunderstand.
They coming after us, girl. The young
GIRLS ARE THEY MAD AT US THINKING WE
TRYING TO TAKE THEIR MEN. WE DON'T WANT
THEM [\h__\h]
I DONE RAISED MINE. I DON'T WANT YOURS.
BUT THEY ON US. THEY ON US. AND THEN I
DID MY RESEARCH AND I FIGURED OUT WHAT'S
GOING ON IN THESE STREETS. AND YOU KNOW
WHAT I REALIZED, MY FELLOW AUNTIES?
THEM POOR WHITE EARS, they tired of air
mattresses.
They tired of Lunchables and fruit
snacks.
They know food supposed to be hot.
They tired of these young [\h__\h]
chicken Alfredo and them to death.
They know it's other things you can do
with ALFREDO SAUCE. THEY KNOW.
THEY DONE [\h__\h] AROUND AND GOT THEM A
MISS WANDA JEAN, HONEY.
You know, and I think any woman in here
over 50 should have a nice little young
piece of something in her back pocket.
Absolutely. KEEP YOUR SKIN TIGHT.
KEEP YOUR UP ON THE TICKET TOPS.
BUT YOU CAN'T GET NO REGULAR white in.
No, man, you got to get a certain type.
You can't get one from a two-parent
household.
>> [screaming]
>> Can't get one with a little college
degree cuz now they think they know
every [\h__\h] thing.
You got to get you one with no hopes, no
dreams.
THEM THE BEST ONES, HONEY. THEY
IMPRESSED WITH SIMPLE [\h__\h] [\h__\h] THAT'S
REGULAR TO US. THEY WALK IN OUR HOUSE
AND THEIR MIND IS BLOWN BY SIMPLE [\h__\h]
LIKE BLINDS
AND DRAPES
area rugs, A MATCHING COFFEE TABLE WITH
TWO END TABLES.
They go in your kitchen and they think
your microwave brand new cuz it's clean.
They lay on your bed doing snow angels
like, "Ooh, your sheets don't move."
[\h__\h] THAT'S A FITTED SHEET.
YOU AIN'T NEVER LAID ON A FITTED sheet
before, baby?
>> [laughter]
>> They don't know what to do when you give
them a matching towel SET. DON'T GIVE
THEM A TOWEL SET AND IT'S ALL RED.
A RED WASHCLOTH, A red hand towel, a red
towel. They look, "Ooh, miss lady, you
fancy."
>> [cheering]
>> They love GOING IN OUR SHOWER AND THE
SHOWER GELS IN there that ARE UNISEX
LIKE SALT AND STONE AND [\h__\h] THEY AIN'T
GOT TO COME OUT THE SHOWER SMELLING LIKE
SWEET PEA.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> You got to get them together, honey.
They love us though, honey.
You young girls, y'all need an auntie in
your life. I've realized that. Y'all do.
Y'all be trying to insult us talking
about, "I ain't auntie." Heifer, you
hope you look this good at 53.
Some of you young girls, you need to
slow your ass down.
You looking raggedy, Laquida.
Might want to slow down, baby.
Looking like you've been through some
things. How you 28 looking 48? Something
ain't right.
It ain't nothing wrong with hoeing,
heifer, but take a whole break.
>> [laughter]
>> Give your coochie a break. Now you're 35
and your [\h__\h] loose like A OLD WALLET.
CAN'T HOLD no money.
Wonder why you're 36 still on the air
mattress in a studio apartment.